<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-22T22:49:35+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">MOHD SAFWAN</title><subtitle>This is me in HTML</subtitle><author><name>Mohd Safwan</name></author><entry><title type="html">Hello World</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/01/hello-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World" /><published>2019-07-01T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-07-01T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/01/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/01/hello-world.html">&lt;p class=&quot;message&quot;&gt;
    “Become antifragile or die” - Taleb Nassim
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h2 id=&quot;who-am-i&quot;&gt;Who am I?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am Mohd Safwan, an undergraduate student at IIT Bombay, and a Computer Vision Engineer at &lt;a href=&quot;https://augle.ai&quot;&gt;Augle AI&lt;/a&gt;. My interests are Deep Learning and Computer Vision. Reach out to me at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:safwaniitb@gmail.com&quot;&gt;safwaniitb@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or connect with me at  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/safwankdb/&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;. Know more about me &lt;a href=&quot;./about&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h2 id=&quot;projects&quot;&gt;Projects&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Projects are good things, perhaps the best of things. In my experience, no good project ever gets completed. Here is a non-exhaustive &lt;a href=&quot;./projects&quot;&gt;list of projects&lt;/a&gt; I own or have contributed to. Apart from this, have a look at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/safwankdb&quot;&gt;my GitHub&lt;/a&gt;. You can find a short (probably outdated) &lt;a href=&quot;./Resume.pdf&quot;&gt;Resume here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;h2 id=&quot;blog&quot;&gt;Blog&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my blog where I try to summarize my thoughts about all kinds of things. Having started recently, I will try to write more often.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Mohd Safwan</name></author><summary type="html">“Become antifragile or die” - Taleb Nassim Who am I? I am Mohd Safwan, an undergraduate student at IIT Bombay, and a Computer Vision Engineer at Augle AI. My interests are Deep Learning and Computer Vision. Reach out to me at safwaniitb@gmail.com or connect with me at LinkedIn. Know more about me here. Projects Projects are good things, perhaps the best of things. In my experience, no good project ever gets completed. Here is a non-exhaustive list of projects I own or have contributed to. Apart from this, have a look at my GitHub. You can find a short (probably outdated) Resume here. Blog This is my blog where I try to summarize my thoughts about all kinds of things. Having started recently, I will try to write more often.</summary></entry></feed>